RG 062:013, Town of Bozrah
Connecticut State Library
Town of Bozrah records
1798-1914
Connecticut State Library
Bozrah (Conn.)
9.5 cubic feet
Tax records for the town of Bozrah.
RG062_013
T000620
Historical Note
The town of Bozrah was incorporated in May 1786 and was taken from Norwich.
Scope and Content
Tax records for the town of Bozrah.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Bozrah -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Bozrah -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Bozrah -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Bozrah -- Registers
Places:
Bozrah (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1798-1914
  - Tax abstracts, 1798, 1799, 1800, 1802, 1808, 1809, 1810, 1811, 1812, 1813, 1815, 1816, 1817, 1818, 1820, 1822, 1823, 1824, undated (3) (Box Box 1)
  - Tax abstracts
    Boxes 4 and 6 are on oversize shelving.
    - 1826, 1827, 1828, 1829, 1830, 1831, 1832, 1833, 1836, 1837, 1839, 1841, 1842, 1845 (Box Box 2)
    - 1846, 1847, 1848, 1849, 1850, 1851, 1852, 1853, 1854 (Box Box 3)
    - 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859, 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865 (Box Box 4)
    - 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869, 1872, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 5)
    - 1870, 1871, 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884 (Box Box 6)
    - 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box Box 7)
    - 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901 (Box Box 8)
    - 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908 (Box Box 9)
    - 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914 (Box Box 10)
  - Tax abstracts, 1834, 1835; 2 volumes (Volume Oversize)